[{"answer": "From the day you married him", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Since when do you listen to me", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Great", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Where is it", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I can. Any child can learn the violin", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I'll teach them to have discipline", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I'll teach them to have discipline", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "They don't have to. If they can help, great", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Just a couple of minutes", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "But this is when they have violin class", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "No. But if he was, I'd tell him the same thing I'm telling you. You shouldn't quit something just because it's hard", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Standing strong doesn't only mean using your legs. You can stand strong on the inside too.  Know what I mean", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I said,", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "It was a happy day", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "He didn't believe you. But I was born. The same day as Grandpa", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Was Daddy happy too", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "My asthma", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh yeah. Maybe it was last week", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Good. Just do the best you can", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Like what", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What's your name", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You hungry, my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Drop dead, my friend", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Was not", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "This is humiliating", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No. A lot of guys are interested in dating you and my friend.  What did you say about me, anyway", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I think you're flat, my friend", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "The B sounded flat", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "That's fantastic", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "And", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " I'll be right in. Start on Minuet One.  What's wrong", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What? Where are you moving", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "What? Where are you moving", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " Has he been hurting you too", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "my friend, can you make sure the charts are still in my bag", "docId": "Music-of-the-Heart.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " Check again, please. And look for my repair kit too", "qsentId": 36}]